<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prometheus Hetzner SD</title>
    <link>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prometheus Hetzner SD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Usage</title>
      <link>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/usage/</guid>
      <description>Installation We won&amp;rsquo;t cover further details how to properly setup Prometheus itself, we will only cover some basic setup based on docker-compose. But if you want to run this service discovery without docker-compose you should be able to adopt that to your needs.
First of all we need to prepare a configuration for Prometheus that includes the service discovery which simply maps to a node exporter.
global: scrape_interval: 1m scrape_timeout: 10s evaluation_interval: 1m scrape_configs: - job_name: node file_sd_configs: - files: [ &amp;#34;/etc/sd/hetzner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes Currently we are covering the most famous installation methods on Kubernetes, you can choose between Kustomize and Helm.
Kustomize We won&amp;rsquo;t cover the installation of Kustomize within this guide, to get it installed and working please read the upstream documentation. After the installation of Kustomize you just need to prepare a kustomization.yml wherever you like similar to this:
apiVersion: kustomize.config.k8s.io/v1beta1 kind: Kustomization namespace: prometheus-hetzner-sd resources: - github.com/promhippie/prometheus-hetzner-sd//deploy/kubernetes?ref=master configMapGenerator: - name: prometheus-hetzner-sd behavior: merge literals: [] secretGenerator: - name: prometheus-hetzner-sd behavior: merge literals: [] After that you can simply execute kustomize build | kubectl apply -f - to get the manifest applied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building</title>
      <link>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/building/</guid>
      <description>As this project is built with Go you need to install Go first. The installation of Go is out of the scope of this document, please follow the official documentation. After the installation of Go you need to get the sources:
git clone https://github.com/promhippie/prometheus-hetzner-sd.git cd prometheus-hetzner-sd/ All required tool besides Go itself are bundled, all you need is part of the Makfile:
make generate build Finally you should have the binary within the bin/ folder now, give it a try with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://promhippie.github.io/prometheus-hetzner-sd/license/</guid>
      <description>This project is licensed under the Apache 2.0 license. For the license of the used libraries you have to check the respective sources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
